Fred Crawford Papers
Marist College Archives and Special Collections
- 6. Lowell Thomas Papers Research File, 6; Boxes: 52 - 169
  - Kennedy Brothers (Publisher), 1936 (Folder 11, Box 105)
  - Kieran, John, 1964 - 1978 (Folder 12, Box 105)
  - Kilgallen, Dorothy, 1936 (Folder 13, Box 105)
  - Killers of the Sea (See Racid [?]), 1948 (Folder 14, Box 105)
  - King, David, 1932 - 1979 (Folder 15, Box 105)
  - Kipling, 1936 - 1937 (Folder 16, Box 105)
  - Kirkman (IOWA), 1894 - 1857 (Folder 17, Box 105)
  - Kirkwood, Joe, 1954 - 1973 (Folder 18, Box 105)
  - Kissinger, 1969 - 1975 (Folder 19, Box 105)
  - Klein, Julius, 1948 - 1975 (Folder 20, Box 105)
  - Knickerbocker Greys, 1933 - 1972 (Folder 21, Box 105)
  - Knight, Charles, 1947 (Folder 22, Box 105)
  - Knight, Kathy, 1964 - 1965 (Folder 23, Box 105)
  - Knoll Cottage, 1956 - 1974 (Folder 24, Box 105)
  - Knope, 1972 (Folder 25, Box 105)
  - Kholer, Walter, 1930 and 1957 (Folder 26, Box 105)
  - Kolb, 1967 (Folder 27, Box 105)
  - KOO, 1967 (Folder 28, Box 105)
  - Korea, 1947 - 1953 (Folder 29, Box 105)
  - Kosmok, Geo, 1940 - 1947 (Folder 30, Box 105)
  - Les Kramer on Celeb Ball, 1940 September 20 (Folder 31, Box 105)
  - Kraus, Edw. [Edward], 1943 (Folder 32, Box 105)
  - Kresge, 1974 (Folder 33, Box 105)
  - Kuck (Tibet, 1969 Tour), 1968 - 1981 (Folder 34, Box 105)
  - Kupferman, Theodore, 1962 - 1967 (Folder 35, Box 105)
  - KWOK, 1960 - 1972 (Folder 36, Box 105)
  - Kyner, 1952 - 1955 (Folder 37, Box 105)
  - La Bianca (DTC), 1957 (Folder 38, Box 105)
  - La Guardia, 1932 - 1978 (Folder 39, Box 105)
  - Labrador - Quebec Expedition, 1932 (Folder 40, Box 105)
  - Lake Placid (Geo. Carroll), 1942 - 1981 (Folder 41, Box 105)
  - Lancaster and Chester Railway, 1966 - 1975 (Folder 42, Box 105)
  - Landers, Ann, 1961 - 1980 (Folder 1, Box 106)
  - Landon, Alf, 1972 - 1975 (Folder 2, Box 106)
  - Lane, Rose Wilder, 1931 - 1979 (Folder 3, Box 106)
  - Lang, Otto [originally 1 file], 1936 - 1958 (Folder 4, Box 106)
  - Lang, Otto [originally 1 file], 1959 - 1967 (Folder 5, Box 106)
  - Lang, Otto [originally 1 file], 1967 - 1973 (Folder 6, Box 106)
  - Lang, Otto [originally 1 file], 1973 - 1981 (Folder 7, Box 106)
  - Lankler, 1935 - 1979 (Folder 8, Box 106)
  - Lankler Re LT Religion, 1963 September 13 (Folder 9, Box 106)
  - Larson, Christine (Barrett), 1936 - 1950? (Folder 10, Box 106)
  - Latady (Exc), 1969 - 1979 (Folder 11, Box 106)
  - Latin, 1931 - 1932 (Folder 12, Box 106)
  - Latter Day Saints, 1949 (Folder 13, Box 106)
  - LauBach, 1969 (Folder 14, Box 106)
  - Laugh, 1931 - 1978 (Folder 15, Box 106)
  - Laugh (Cripps), 1942 - 1950 (Folder 16, Box 106)
  - Laugh (Dog is Tail), 1941 - 1942 (Folder 17, Box 106)
  - Laugh (Fat Lady), 1978 (Folder 18, Box 106)
  - Laugh - Flint, 1942 April 30 (Folder 1, Box 107)
  - Laugh (Wac Chest), 1946 (Folder 2, Box 107)
  - Lauterbach, 1930 (Folder 3, Box 107)
  - Lawrence, D. H., 1932 (Folder 4, Box 107)
  - Lawrence, J. D., 1962 - 1965 (Folder 5, Box 107)
  - Lawrence - Smith School, 1932 - 1947 (Folder 6, Box 107)
  - Layacana, Maria, 1950? (Folder 7, Box 107)
  - Leaves Req [Request], 1936 (Folder 8, Box 107)
  - Le Seuer, 1966 (Folder 9, Box 107)
  - Lectures, 1934 - 1943 (Folder 10, Box 107)
  - Lecture Requests, 1938 - 1943 (Folder 11, Box 107)
  - Lee, Mabel Barbee [originally 1 file], 1936 - 1953 (Folder 12, Box 107)
  - Lee, Mabel Barbee [originally 1 file], 1953 - 1955 (Folder 13, Box 107)
  - Lee, Mabel Barbee [originally 1 file], 1955 - 1959 (Folder 14, Box 107)
  - Lee, Mabel Barbee [originally 1 file], 1959 - 1968 (Folder 15, Box 107)
  - Lee, Mabel Barbee [originally 1 file], 1968 - 1980 (Folder 16, Box 107)
  - Lee on Victor, Dr. H., 1957 November 30 (Folder 1, Box 108)
  - Legal and Estate Stuff [originally 1 file], 1931 - 1975 (Folder 2, Box 108)
  - Legal and Estate Stuff [originally 1 file], 1975 - 1982 (Folder 3, Box 108)
  - Legal and Estate Stuff [originally 1 file], 1982 - 1983 (Folder 4, Box 108)
  - Legion of Honor, 1938 - 1952 (Folder 5, Box 108)
  - Legion of Valor, 1933 - 1936 (Folder 6, Box 108)
  - Lehmann, Josephine, 1928 - 1979 (Folder 7, Box 108)
  - Lehr, Lew, 1939 - 1941 (Folder 8, Box 108)
  - Leigh, W. Colston (Bureau), 1940 (Folder 9, Box 108)
  - Leister - Sons, 1940 - 1942 (Folder 10, Box 108)
  - Lerch, John, 1953 - 1970 (Folder 11, Box 108)
  - Lewis, Boyd, 1971 (Folder 12, Box 108)
  - Lewis, Fulton, 1958 - 1966 (Folder 13, Box 108)
  - Lewis, Hobe, 1970 (Folder 14, Box 108)
  - Lewis, Sinclair, 1939 (Folder 15, Box 108)
  - Lewisburg Flap, 1933 (Folder 16, Box 108)
  - Liability?, 1941 (Folder 17, Box 108)
  - Libel, 1948 (Folder 18, Box 108)
  - Liberty (Oursler), 1931 - 1940 (Folder 19, Box 108)
  - Libi, 1979 (Folder 20, Box 108)
  - Library, 1938 (Folder 21, Box 108)
  - Liddell Hart, 1955 (Folder 22, Box 108)
  - Liddle, 1933 - 1936 (Folder 23, Box 108)
  - LIFE Mag [Magazine], 1937 - 1949 (Folder 24, Box 108)
  - Liggett, 1936 (Folder 25, Box 108)
  - Lilley (Lhasa), 1978 - 1979 (Folder 26, Box 108)
  - Lincoln Ctr. [Center], 1960 - 1963 (Folder 27, Box 108)
  - Lindbergh, 1937 - 1981 (Folder 28, Box 108)
  - Lindbergh Trial, undated (Folder 29, Box 108)
  - Line Charges, undated (Folder 30, Box 108)
  - Linkletter, 1962 - 1966 (Folder 31, Box 108)
  - Lion Has Wings, 1939 - 1940 (Folder 32, Box 108)
  - Lippincott, 1951 (Folder 1, Box 109)
  - Lipscomb, W. P., 1935 - 1959 (Folder 2, Box 109)
  - LIT Digest, 1930 - 1980 (Folder 3, Box 109)
  - Literary Tea (H. Allen Smith), 1930 September 1 (Folder 4, Box 109)
  - Little, Brown, 1931 - 1939 (Folder 5, Box 109)
  - Live - Mike Slips, 1939 - 1944 (Folder 6, Box 109)
  - Liveright, 1931 - 1936 (Folder 7, Box 109)
  - Locust Farm, 1931 - 1977 (Folder 8, Box 109)
  - Lodwick Aircraft, 1948 (Folder 9, Box 109)
  - Logan (Ski), 1950 (Folder 10, Box 109)
  - Loman (Livestock Drive), 1933 - 1966 (Folder 11, Box 109)
  - London, Jack, 1969 (Folder 12, Box 109)
  - London Airport Interview, 1967 (Folder 13, Box 109)
  - London Debts, 1932 - 1941 (Folder 14, Box 109)
  - Long, Huey, 1935 (Folder 15, Box 109)
  - Long (Publisher), 1931 - 1933 (Folder 16, Box 109)
  - Longest Hole, 1979 (Folder 17, Box 109)
  - Lonvgevity Record (Radio), 1950 (Folder 18, Box 109)
  - Loos, Anita, 1950 (Folder 19, Box 109)
  - Lord Forrest (Saga and C. Chests), 1936 - 1940 (Folder 20, Box 109)
  - Lot (Alta), 1956 - 1957 (Folder 21, Box 109)
  - Louis, Joe, 1938 - 1956 (Folder 22, Box 109)
  - Low, Catherine, 1942 (Folder 23, Box 109)
  - Lowell Thomas Remembers, 1975 - 1979 (Folder 24, Box 109)
  - Lowell Thomas Remembers A. E. Smith, 1977 (Folder 25, Box 109)
  - LT Address, 1948 (Folder 26, Box 109)
  - Lowell Thomas and America, 1975 - 1978 (Folder 27, Box 109)
  - L. T. [Lowell Thomas] on Announcers, 1943 (Folder 28, Box 109)
  - LT [Lowell Thomas] on Anti - Semitism, 1941 (Folder 29, Box 109)
  - LT [Lowell Thomas] Anniversary, 1940 (Folder 30, Box 109)
  - LT [Lowell Thomas] Aplomb, 1946 (Folder 31, Box 109)
  - LT [Lowell Thomas] Apology, 1963 (Folder 32, Box 109)
  - LT [Lowell Thomas] Archives, 1955 - 1976 (Folder 33, Box 109)
  - LT [Lowell Thomas] Articles, 1936 - 1948 (Folder 34, Box 109)
  - LT [Lowell Thomas] on Articles (BSV), 1956 February 13 (Folder 35, Box 109)
  - LT [Lowell Thomas] and Astrology, 1934 - 1939 (Folder 36, Box 109)
  - LT [Lowell Thomas] on Australia, 1964 (Folder 37, Box 109)
  - LT [Lowell Thomas] Authority, 1938 - 1964 (Folder 38, Box 109)
  - LT [Lowell Thomas] on Autographs, 1944 (Folder 39, Box 109)
  - LT [Lowell Thomas] Awards, 1937 - 1981 (Folder 40, Box 109)
  - LT [Lowell Thomas] on Banquets, 1967 - 1972 (Folder 41, Box 109)
  - LT [Lowell Thomas] Baseball Trophy, 1940 (Folder 42, Box 109)
  - LT [Lowell Thomas]: Best Advice (LT [Lowell Thomas] Bias), 1931 (Folder 43, Box 109)
  - LT [Lowell Thomas] Bias, 1934 - 1975 (Folder 1, Box 110)
  - LT [Lowell Thomas] Bible Quotation, 1976 (Folder 2, Box 110)
  - LT [Lowell Thomas] on Bible Verses, 1953 (Folder 3, Box 110)
  - LT [Lowell Thomas] Bios, 1922 - 1981 (Folder 4, Box 110)
  - LT [Lowell Thomas] on Black and White, 1957 (Folder 5, Box 110)
  - LT [Lowell Thomas] Boils, 1935 (Folder 6, Box 110)
  - LT [Lowell Thomas] Book collecting, 1976 January (Folder 7, Box 110)
  - LT [Lowell Thomas] Book Plates, 1974 (Folder 8, Box 110)
  - LT [Lowell Thomas] Books (?), 1953 - 1958 (Folder 9, Box 110)
  - LT [Lowell Thomas] Broadcast History, 1968 (Folder 10, Box 110)
  - LT [Lowell Thomas] and Burial Move, 1940 (Folder 11, Box 110)
  - LT [Lowell Thomas] Campus, 1967 (Folder 12, Box 110)
  - LT [Lowell Thomas] on Canada, 1942 - 1960 (Folder 13, Box 110)
  - LT [Lowell Thomas] Candy?, 1935 (Folder 14, Box 110)
  - LT [Lowell Thomas] Career, 1932 - 1960 (Folder 15, Box 110)
  - LT [Lowell Thomas] Cartoon, 1943 (Folder 16, Box 110)
  - LT [Lowell Thomas] Claim, 1942 (Folder 17, Box 110)
  - LT [Lowell Thomas] on changes in LT's [Lowell Thomas'] Lifetime, 1892 - 1976 (Folder 18, Box 110)
  - LT [Lowell Thomas] on Collaboration, 1944 (Folder 19, Box 110)
  - LT [Lowell Thomas] Colonel, 1933 - 1934 (Folder 20, Box 110)
  - LT [Lowell Thomas] Column, 1934 - 1976 (Folder 21, Box 110)
  - LT [Lowell Thomas] on Communications History and Radio Firsts, undated (Folder 22, Box 110)
  - LT [Lowell Thomas] on Conscription, 1945 (Folder 23, Box 110)
  - LT [Lowell Thomas] on Control, 1944 (1976) (Folder 24, Box 110)
  - LT [Lowell Thomas] on Conservation, 1971 (Folder 25, Box 110)
  - LT [Lowell Thomas] on Corrections, 1935 - 1942 (Folder 26, Box 110)
  - LT [Lowell Thomas] on Correspondence, 1944 (Folder 27, Box 110)
  - LT [Lowell Thomas] Courtesy, 1952 (Folder 28, Box 110)
  - LT [Lowell Thomas] Credit Rept [Report], 1940 (Folder 29, Box 110)
  - LT [Lowell Thomas] on Critics and Editors, 1953 (Folder 30, Box 110)
  - LT [Lowell Thomas] Credo, 1978 (Folder 31, Box 110)
  - LT [Lowell Thomas] on Divorce, 1968 (Folder 32, Box 110)
  - LT [Lowell Thomas] Dahlia, 1940 (Folder 33, Box 110)
  - LT [Lowell Thomas] Daily Schedule, 1940 (Folder 34, Box 110)
  - LT [Lowell Thomas] Day (QH), 1972 (Folder 35, Box 110)
  - LT [Lowell Thomas] Death, 1981 August 29 (Folder 36, Box 110)
  - LT [Lowell Thomas] Discoverer, 1975 - 1981 (Folder 37, Box 110)
  - LT [Lowell Thomas] Double, 1957 (Folder 38, Box 110)
  - LT [Lowell Thomas] Drinking, 1939 (Folder 39, Box 110)
  - LT [Lowell Thomas] Early Obit [Obituary], 1962 (Folder 40, Box 110)
  - LT [Lowell Thomas] on " Early Days in Radio ", 1966 - 1975 (Folder 41, Box 110)
  - LT [Lowell Thomas] on East Africa, 1972 (Folder 1, Box 111)
  - LT [Lowell Thomas] on Edit Pol, 1955 (Folder 2, Box 111)
  - LT [Lowell Thomas] Editor, 1941 (Folder 3, Box 111)
  - LT [Lowell Thomas] on Education, 1962 (Folder 4, Box 111)
  - LT [Lowell Thomas] Eleanor Roosevelt, 1979 (Folder 5, Box 111)
  - LT [Lowell Thomas] on Embarrassing Moments, 1979 (Folder 6, Box 111)
  - LT [Lowell Thomas] " Endorse ", 1947 (Folder 7, Box 111)
  - LT [Lowell Thomas] on Endorsements, 1956 (Folder 8, Box 111)
  - LT [Lowell Thomas] Example, 1933 - 1981 (Folder 9, Box 111)
  - LT [Lowell Thomas] Fame, 1933 - 1978 (Folder 10, Box 111)
  - LT [Lowell Thomas] on Fame, 1935 - 1980 (Folder 11, Box 111)
  - LT [Lowell Thomas] on Fan Mail, 1952 (Folder 12, Box 111)
  - LT [Lowell Thomas] on Film and Film Books, 1937 - 1940 (Folder 13, Box 111)
  - LT [Lowell Thomas] " Film Formula ", 1957 May VSSR (Folder 14, Box 111)
  - LT [Lowell Thomas] Film Q - Aire, 1980 (Folder 15, Box 111)
  - LT [Lowell Thomas] " Firsts ", 1934 - 1970 (Folder 16, Box 111)
  - LT [Lowell Thomas] Flyer?, 1944 (Folder 17, Box 111)
  - LT [Lowell Thomas] Flying Fortress, 1943 (Folder 18, Box 111)
  - LT [Lowell Thomas] on Food, 1931 - 1965 (Folder 19, Box 111)
  - LT [Lowell Thomas] on Foreign Correspondents, 1959 (Folder 20, Box 111)
  - LT [Lowell Thomas] on France, 1943 (Folder 21, Box 111)
  - LT [Lowell Thomas] Fraternities (Kappa Sigma), 1939 (Folder 22, Box 111)
  - LT [Lowell Thomas] Fraternities, 1961 (Folder 23, Box 111)
  - " LT [Lowell Thomas] " on Freedom, 1958 (Folder 24, Box 111)
  - LT [Lowell Thomas] on FRT, 1938 - 1975 (Folder 25, Box 111)
  - LT [Lowell Thomas]/FRT, 1966 (Folder 26, Box 111)
  - LT [Lowell Thomas] on FRT Accident, 1951 (Folder 27, Box 111)
  - LT [Lowell Thomas] on Future, 1947 (Folder 28, Box 111)
  - LT [Lowell Thomas] Games, 1933 - 1951 (Folder 29, Box 111)
  - LT [Lowell Thomas] Generosity, 1931 - 1978 (Folder 30, Box 111)
  - Gen - Caldwell, 1936 - 1937 (Folder 31, Box 111)
  - LT [Lowell Thomas] Goals, 1979 (Folder 32, Box 111)
  - LT [Lowell Thomas] on Greatest Adventure, 1931 (Folder 33, Box 111)
  - LT [Lowell Thomas] Handwriting, 1934 - 1975 (Folder 34, Box 111)
  - LT [Lowell Thomas] Header, 1968 (Folder 35, Box 111)
  - LT [Lowell Thomas] Health, 1934 - 1981 (Folder 36, Box 111)
  - LT [Lowell Thomas] on his own success (QI, Braley), 1940? (Folder 37, Box 111)
  - LT [Lowell Thomas] " Home Site ", 1940 (Folder 38, Box 111)
  - LT [Lowell Thomas] on Hoover, 1969 - 1978 (Folder 39, Box 111)
  - LT [Lowell Thomas] Hospital, 1947 (Folder 40, Box 111)
  - LT [Lowell Thomas] Humor, 1947 (Folder 41, Box 111)
  - LT [Lowell Thomas] Imposter, 1950 (Folder 42, Box 111)
  - LT [Lowell Thomas] and Indian Tribe, 1931 (Folder 43, Box 111)
  - LT [Lowell Thomas] Influence, 1934 - 1980 (Folder 44, Box 111)
  - LT [Lowell Thomas] Influence, 1934 - 1980 (Folder 45, Box 111)
  - LT [Lowell Thomas] " Insults ", undated (Folder 46, Box 111)
  - LT [Lowell Thomas] Interview (1908), 1978 (Folder 47, Box 111)
  - LT [Lowell Thomas] Insurance, 1963 - 1966 (Folder 1, Box 112)
  - Intro - > Jack Jingle's Wish, 1953 (Folder 2, Box 112)
  - LT [Lowell Thomas] Intros, 1964 - 1977 (Folder 3, Box 112)
  - LT [Lowell Thomas] Island, 1946 - 1947 (Folder 4, Box 112)
  - LT [Lowell Thomas] Joiner, 1911 - 1959 (Folder 5, Box 112)
  - LT [Lowell Thomas] Joke, 1935 - 1942 (Folder 6, Box 112)
  - LT [Lowell Thomas] on journalism, 1979 (Folder 7, Box 112)
  - LT [Lowell Thomas] Juuenal Quotation, 1957 (Folder 8, Box 112)
  - LT [Lowell Thomas] Kind of Help, 1954 - 1955 (Folder 9, Box 112)
  - LT [Lowell Thomas] on Kennedy/Nixon Debates, 1966 (Folder 10, Box 112)
  - LT [Lowell Thomas] on Kissinger, 1975 (Folder 11, Box 112)
  - LT [Lowell Thomas] on Laugh, 1947 - 1948 May 28 (Folder 12, Box 112)
  - LT [Lowell Thomas] on Law, 1935 (Folder 13, Box 112)
  - LT [Lowell Thomas] on Lecture Bus, 1956? (Folder 14, Box 112)
  - LT [Lowell Thomas] on Lectures (BSV), 1948 December 8 (Folder 15, Box 112)
  - LT [Lowell Thomas] on Leftist News, 1971 (Folder 16, Box 112)
  - LT [Lowell Thomas] on " Let's Put UN Capital on the High Seas ", 1950 June 11 (Folder 17, Box 112)
  - LT [Lowell Thomas] Letters, 1977 (Folder 18, Box 112)
  - LT [Lowell Thomas] on Live Charges and Tour Logistics, 1946 - 1953 (Folder 19, Box 112)
  - LT [Lowell Thomas] Look - Alike, 1948 (Folder 20, Box 112)
  - LT [Lowell Thomas] Measurements, 1977 (Folder 21, Box 112)
  - LT [Lowell Thomas] and Mail, 1940 (Folder 22, Box 112)
  - LT [Lowell Thomas] Meet, 1963 - 1968 (Folder 23, Box 112)
  - LT [Lowell Thomas] Miffed, 1940 - 1943 (Folder 24, Box 112)
  - LT [Lowell Thomas] MISC AMX, 1964 (Folder 25, Box 112)
  - LT [Lowell Thomas] on Motner, 1941 (Folder 26, Box 112)
  - LT [Lowell Thomas] Mtns. [Mountains], 1948 (Folder 27, Box 112)
  - LT [Lowell Thomas] Mums, 1947 (Folder 28, Box 112)
  - LT [Lowell Thomas] on Murrow Visit, 1956 (Folder 29, Box 112)
  - LT [Lowell Thomas] on Music, 1940 (Folder 30, Box 112)
  - LT [Lowell Thomas] name (Jackson), 1956 (Folder 31, Box 112)
  - LT [Lowell Thomas] on New Guinea, 1968 (Folder 32, Box 112)
  - LT [Lowell Thomas] on NYT [New York Times], 1978 (Folder 33, Box 112)
  - LT [Lowell Thomas] on News, 1956 (Folder 34, Box 112)
  - LT [Lowell Thomas] on News Broadcasting, 1939 - 1948 (Folder 35, Box 112)
  - LT [Lowell Thomas] on News of Week, 1936 (Folder 36, Box 112)
  - LT [Lowell Thomas] on Non - Fiction Films (New G [Guinea]), undated (Folder 37, Box 112)
  - LT [Lowell Thomas] Novel, 1932 (Folder 38, Box 112)
  - LT [Lowell Thomas] Obit [Obituary] (Bush G. Hosted), 1981 (Folder 39, Box 112)
  - LT [Lowell Thomas] Obits [Obituaries], 1981 (Folder 40, Box 112)
  - LT [Lowell Thomas] Peony, 1946 - 1954 (Folder 41, Box 112)
  - LT [Lowell Thomas] on Prep for Broadcasting career, 1950 (Folder 42, Box 112)
  - LT [Lowell Thomas] on Pipeline, 1972 (Folder 43, Box 112)
  - LT [Lowell Thomas] on Pol [Politics?], Anti S [Anti-Semitic], etc., circa 1939 (Folder 44, Box 112)
  - LT [Lowell Thomas] Politics, 1934 - 1981 (Folder 45, Box 112)
  - LT [Lowell Thomas] Portrait (Kappa Sigma), 1978 (Folder 46, Box 112)
  - LT [Lowell Thomas] Presidency, 1939 - 1979 (Folder 47, Box 112)
  - LT [Lowell Thomas] Press Pass (Louis), 1946 (Folder 48, Box 112)
  - LT [Lowell Thomas] on Pronunciation, 1965? (Folder 49, Box 112)
  - LT [Lowell Thomas] on Prosper, 1964 October 20 (Folder 50, Box 112)
  - LT [Lowell Thomas] on Publicity, 1970 (Folder 51, Box 112)
  - LT [Lowell Thomas] on Publishing, 1952 (Folder 52, Box 112)
  - LT [Lowell Thomas] on Pyle, 1945 May 16 (Folder 53, Box 112)
  - LT [Lowell Thomas] on Q Lake and LT on ski Pros, 1943 (Folder 54, Box 112)
  - LT [Lowell Thomas] on Race, 1975 (Folder 55, Box 112)
  - LT [Lowell Thomas] Race (Ski), 1951 - 1953 (Folder 56, Box 112)
  - LT [Lowell Thomas] on Radio and Speaking, 1944 (Folder 57, Box 112)
  - LT [Lowell Thomas] on Ratinas, 1944 (Folder 58, Box 112)
  - LT [Lowell Thomas] Record, 1971 (Folder 1, Box 113)
  - LT [Lowell Thomas] Pub [Publication], 1925 - 1981 (Folder 2, Box 113)
  - LT [Lowell Thomas] rub [Publication] - noble, 1976 (Folder 3, Box 113)
  - LT [Lowell Thomas] " Relax ", circa 1938 (Folder 4, Box 113)
  - LT [Lowell Thomas] on Religion, 1942 - 1973 (Folder 5, Box 113)
  - LT [Lowell Thomas] Reputation, 1973 - 1974 (Folder 6, Box 113)
  - LT [Lowell Thomas] on Requests, 1955 (Folder 7, Box 113)
  - LT [Lowell Thomas] - > LTJ [Lowell Thomas, Jr.] on Reviews, 1952 (Folder 8, Box 113)
  - LT [Lowell Thomas] " Reserve ", 1961 - 1974 (Folder 9, Box 113)
  - LT [Lowell Thomas] Responds to Q's [Questions], 1956 - 1975 (Folder 10, Box 113)
  - LT [Lowell Thomas] " Reticence ", 1932? (Folder 11, Box 113)
  - LT [Lowell Thomas] Retirement, 1970 - 1981 (Folder 12, Box 113)
  - LT [Lowell Thomas] Retirement, 1970 - 1981 (Folder 13, Box 113)
  - LT [Lowell Thomas] Room, 1956 - 1957 (Folder 14, Box 113)
  - LT [Lowell Thomas] Rose, undated (Folder 15, Box 113)
  - LT [Lowell Thomas] Schedule, 1932 (Folder 16, Box 113)
  - LT [Lowell Thomas] on Scoops, 1977 (Folder 17, Box 113)
  - LT [Lowell Thomas] on Scripts, 1944 (Folder 18, Box 113)
  - LT [Lowell Thomas] Series, 1932 (Folder 19, Box 113)
  - LT [Lowell Thomas] on " Show ", 1968 (Folder 20, Box 113)
  - LT [Lowell Thomas] Signatures, 1956 (Folder 21, Box 113)
  - LT [Lowell Thomas] on Ski Film, 1953 - 1954 (Folder 22, Box 113)
  - LT [Lowell Thomas] Ski Jump, 1949 (Folder 23, Box 113)
  - LT [Lowell Thomas] " Smear ", 1946 (Folder 24, Box 113)
  - LT [Lowell Thomas] Social Security Account # [Number], 1937 (Folder 25, Box 113)
  - LT [Lowell Thomas] on South Seas, 1959 (Folder 26, Box 113)
  - LT [Lowell Thomas] on Speaking, circa 1950s (Folder 27, Box 113)
  - LT [Lowell Thomas] on Speaking Bureaus " Then and Now ", 1972 (Folder 28, Box 113)
  - LT [Lowell Thomas] Soliciting, 1938 - 1959 (Folder 29, Box 113)
  - LT [Lowell Thomas] Speaking Rate, 1944 (Folder 30, Box 113)
  - LT [Lowell Thomas] on Speech (? - Aire), 1951 (Folder 31, Box 113)
  - LT [Lowell Thomas] on Sponsors, 1967 (Folder 32, Box 113)
  - Lowell Thomas Sponsorship, 1932 - 1981 (Folder 1, Box 114)
  - LT [Lowell Thomas] Stationary, undated (Folder 2, Box 114)
  - LT [Lowell Thomas] Subbing, 1939 (Folder 3, Box 114)
  - LT [Lowell Thomas] on Success, 1954 (Folder 4, Box 114)
  - LT [Lowell Thomas] suing the Press, 1969 (Folder 5, Box 114)
  - LT [Lowell Thomas] on Superstition, 1942 (Folder 6, Box 114)
  - LT [Lowell Thomas] Tapes, 1980 (Folder 7, Box 114)
  - LT [Lowell Thomas] on Tel [Television] Show (Heyn), 1962 (Folder 8, Box 114)
  - LT [Lowell Thomas] on Third World War, 1945 - 1948 (Folder 9, Box 114)
  - LT [Lowell Thomas] Tours, 1938 - 1970 (Folder 10, Box 114)
  - LT [Lowell Thomas] on Travel, 1959 (Folder 11, Box 114)
  - LT [Lowell Thomas] Travel Library, 1968 (Folder 12, Box 114)
  - LT [Lowell Thomas] Travelogues, 1920 - 1924 (Folder 13, Box 114)
  - LT [Lowell Thomas] Tulip, 1939 (Folder 14, Box 114)
  - LT [Lowell Thomas] on TV vs. Radio, 1952 - 1973 (Folder 15, Box 114)
  - LT [Lowell Thomas] and TV, 1959 (Folder 16, Box 114)
  - LT [Lowell Thomas] on TV Nego (Ski), 1961 (Folder 17, Box 114)
  - LT [Lowell Thomas] University, 1972 (Folder 18, Box 114)
  - LT [Lowell Thomas] on U. S. Sights, 1975 (Folder 19, Box 114)
  - LT [Lowell Thomas] on Variety, 1953 (Folder 20, Box 114)
  - LT [Lowell Thomas] on War News, 1943 (Folder 21, Box 114)
  - LT [Lowell Thomas] Wedding 1917, 1973 (Folder 22, Box 114)
  - LT [Lowell Thomas] Wedding, 1977 (Folder 23, Box 114)
  - LT [Lowell Thomas] on " What About the Future? ", 1974 (Folder 24, Box 114)
  - LT [Lowell Thomas] on Who Most Like to Meet, 1974 (Folder 25, Box 114)
  - LT [Lowell Thomas] Wills, 1932 - 1944 (Folder 26, Box 114)
  - LT [Lowell Thomas] on Women, 1935 - 1964 (Folder 27, Box 114)
  - LT [Lowell Thomas] on Writing, undated (Folder 28, Box 114)
  - LT [Lowell Thomas] on Writing Autobiography, 1966 (Folder 29, Box 114)
  - LT [Lowell Thomas] WWII Leaders, 1943 (Folder 30, Box 114)
  - LTJ [Lowell Thomas Jr.] [1 of 4 from original file], 1931 - 1944 (Folder 31, Box 114)
  - LTJ [Lowell Thomas Jr.] [2 of 4 from original file], 1944 - 1954 (Folder 32, Box 114)
  - LTJ [Lowell Thomas Jr.] [3 of 4 from original file], 1954 - 1961 (Folder 1, Box 115)
  - LTJ [Lowell Thomas Jr.] [4 of 4 from original file], 1962 - 1966 (Folder 2, Box 115)
  - LTJ [Lowell Thomas Jr.] [1 of 4 from original file], 1956 - 1962 (Folder 3, Box 115)
  - LTJ [Lowell Thomas Jr.] [2 of 4 from original file], 1962 - 1963 (Folder 4, Box 115)
  - LTJ [Lowell Thomas Jr.] [3 of 4 from original file], 1963 - 1965 (Folder 5, Box 115)
  - LTJ [Lowell Thomas Jr.] [4 of 4 from original file], 1965 - 1966 (Folder 6, Box 115)
  - LTJ [Lowell Thomas Jr.] [1 of 5 from original file], 1967 - 1969 (Folder 7, Box 115)
  - LTJ [Lowell Thomas Jr.] [2 of 5 from original file], 1969 - 1973 (Folder 8, Box 115)
  - LTJ [Lowell Thomas Jr.] [3 of 5 from original file], 1973 - 1974 (Folder 9, Box 115)
  - LTJ [Lowell Thomas Jr.] [4 of 5 from original file], 1974 - 1976 (Folder 10, Box 115)
  - LTJ [Lowell Thomas Jr.] [5 of 5 from original file], 1954 - 1961; 1976 - 1981 (Folder 1, Box 116)
  - LTJ [Lowell Thomas Jr.], 1962 - 1966; undated (Folder 2, Box 116)
  - LTJ [Lowell Thomas Jr.] Alaska Film 1940, 1956 - 1962; 1940 - 1962 (Folder 3, Box 116)
  - Alaska + LTJ [Lowell Thomas Jr.], 1962 - 1963; 1959 - 1960 (Folder 4, Box 116)
  - LTJ [Lowell Thomas Jr.] Alaska Salute, 1963 - 1965; 1961 (Folder 5, Box 116)
  - LTJ [Lowell Thomas Jr.] Am [American] Col [Colony] (Italy), 1965 - 1966; 1953 - 1956 (Folder 6, Box 116)
  - LTJ [Lowell Thomas Jr.] and OH Board, 1967 - 1969; 1958 (Folder 7, Box 116)
  - LTJ [Lowell Thomas Jr.] & Tay, 1969 - 1973; 1954 (Folder 8, Box 116)
  - LTJ [Lowell Thomas Jr.] " Assist ", 1973 - 1974; 1948 (Folder 9, Box 116)
  - LTJ [Lowell Thomas Jr.] Bikini, 1974 - 1976; 1946 (Folder 10, Box 116)
  - LTJ [Lowell Thomas Jr.] Bios, 1948 - 1980 (Folder 11, Box 116)
  - LTJ [Lowell Thomas Jr.] Bohemian Grove, 1953 - 1963 (Folder 12, Box 116)
  - LTJ [Lowell Thomas Jr.] & Carnegie Hall Books, 1965 October 20 (Folder 13, Box 116)
  - LTJ [Lowell Thomas Jr.] Cin [Cinerama], 1953 - 1962 (Folder 14, Box 116)
  - Congress LTJ [Lowell Thomas Jr.], 1962 (Folder 15, Box 116)
  - LTJ [Lowell Thomas Jr.] Critic, 1972 (Folder 16, Box 116)